{
    "subject": "resource/Dolores_Guinness",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Germany",
    "human_readable": "Dolores Guinness was born in Germany.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9722904562950134,
            "question": "Was Dolores Guinness born outside of Germany?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9145937561988831,
            "question": "Dolores Guinness is German?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8282598853111267,
            "question": "Is Dolores Guinness's birthplace in Europe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7998983263969421,
            "question": "Dolores Guinness has German citizenship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7915596961975098,
            "question": "Where was Dolores Guinness born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6783921718597412,
            "question": "Is Dolores Guinness's birthplace a European country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6108862161636353,
            "question": "What nationality is Dolores Guinness?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.573112428188324,
            "question": "What country is Dolores Guinness from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5114830732345581,
            "question": "Where did Dolores Guinness grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4100457727909088,
            "question": "In which country did Dolores Guinness spend her early years?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dolores Guinness was born in Germany.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5537_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Dolores Guinness grow up?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5537_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Dolores Guinness from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5537_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Dolores Guinness?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5537_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5537_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5537_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5537_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5537_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5537_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5537_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5537_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5537_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5537_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5537_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents contain information about Dolores Guinness, and according to one of the documents, she is described as a \"German-born socialite\". This suggests that Dolores Guinness was indeed born in Germany."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents describe Dolores Guinness as a \"German-born socialite,\" which supports the statement that she was born in Germany."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}